Ladies and gentlemen, Crashers Clay.
>> Hello. Can you hear me now?
>> We can hear you loud and clear, brother.
How you doing?
>> Doing good. I uh had to switch over to
my phone to get it to work, I guess. So,
>> no worries, man. We can hear you loud
and clear. And uh yeah, we're just doing
a little Aster live stream. How crazy
this token's three days old this launch.
I guess like a two and a half days old
crash. It's a baby and it's currently I
know you called it around 3540 cents.
It's more than double. tripled pretty
much tripled since then. What's your
first first thoughts on on Asterin, I
guess? Why was the conviction so strong
when you first saw it?
>> Dude, so many things. Uh people don't
realize how bullish it is actually in my
opinion and that's why I kind of wanted
to come on and explain a couple things
about it that I think a lot of people
don't realize. So, one of the first
things I think people don't realize is
like CZ, Justin Sun,
uh, and not even just them too, but like
most projects in the top 50, bro, they
all have like 80% plus supply in the in
the founder team foundation's hands. But
specifically like CZ and and BNBcoin, I
think a lot of there's been like a lot
of
the posts I've seen where they own like
90% plus.
>> Yep.
>> Now look at the chart of B&B. It just
hit a,000 bucks. It's like one of the
most bullish charts. Actually, I stopped
charting things against ETH almost. And
I feel like it's actually smarter to
chart things against BNB because
actually BNB has just been a far
stronger ETH, you know. But anyways,
that for me was instantly one of the
most bullish factors. When when I saw
this, I was like, okay, I already know
CZ probably owns 90% at least. Then I
saw a post says he's got 92%.
So that's already super bullish in my in
my eyes because CZ has no reason really
to sell. He's already his net worth is
like $80 billion. So a lot of people
will pull that up and be like, "Oh,
that's bearish." And me that's literally
the opposite point like, "Holy [__] he
he's that's so bullish." There's going
to be like way less selling pressure on
this, you know?
>> And I I I I I hear that and I I agree.
Now, why do you think it is CZ and maybe
it's not somebody else, you know, that
that has access to the the the the tell
you
>> someone working with Aster.
>> Yeah. Well, one thing was uh months ago
he was posting about
um I think it was because they stop
hunted James Win or someone else or or
maybe it was stop hunting some other
trade on hype. And so then he made his
post about why,
>> you know, it would be interesting time
if someone made a deck with the dark
order books and stuff. And so that was
already like foreshadowing or hinting
the future platform. And he was like,
"If anyone's building it, DM me. No
guarantee I'll respond, but you know,
maybe I will." And obviously, when you
have this much power, this much money,
why would you back anyone besides
yourself and your own team? Why would
you chance working with some bozo who's
going to rug you? Uh, you don't you
don't take chances like that once you're
that big and that responsible. So, it's
undeniable in my opinion. Like,
>> you know, if you're going to back it
like that, it's either you or like your
in-house team at Binance.
>> So, it's not really I mean, like it's
like a 99.9% chance in my opinion. Like
I said, you don't take a chance on like
a firsttime dev or some guy who who just
tells you like you can trust my work.
I've done great projects in the past,
but you never work with him. So, it's
just automatically ruled out in my
opinion. So yeah, cuz I mean, can you
imagine if he trusts some, you know,
[__] dev that never worked with him
before and that guy just rugs it and how
bad that looks for BMBB and buying it.
It's just it's not a risk you can take
once you get that big. So
>> you're you're 100% right. Now you you
mentioned the dark pools and I want to
play this video. You quote tweeted it
first off. I'll read your quote tweet.
We're going to play the video for the
audience cuz I watched this and I was
like, "Oh, so we're comparing Aster to
other decentralized exchanges, but Aster
is in a league of its own." Let me read
your quote tweet first and then we'll
get into the actual uh video that CZ
says, and I'd love to get your thoughts
on it and maybe like break it down for
people who don't understand it. But, uh,
you said Aster to $100 per coin doesn't
even even sound so crazy if you had just
got done watching this video instead of
listening to Hyper Virgin. and it's a
video from CZ Binance on uh for Rock's
podcast Rug Radio. Let's listen to it
and then afterwards if you can kind of
explain why this is so bullish for
Aster.
>> Uh we invest very heavily in
decentralized exchanges. The DEX per the
decentralized DEX per are a huge market
as you mentioned
>> and I think that's that's just getting
started. There's so much more there's so
much more to do. I think the
>> uh the current model where everything's
fully transparent may or may not be the
best model. Um because uh uh yeah, you
can see a big whale putting a $300
million short. U but the guy who really
want to do $300 million short don't want
you to see it,
>> right? So the guys were putting that
there.
>> Yeah, there's a game. There's for sure a
game,
>> right? It's it's for his effect.
>> Uh whereas a real large traders like
institutions. That's why traditionally
dark pools are way bigger than uh uh
what we call lit order books. Um yeah.
So I think this there's a lot of room to
to grow. But I do think that future is
decentralized. um in the future DEX is
going to be bigger than uh CEX and we
want to invest heavily in those areas.
Yeah, we want to invest in the things
that will overturn that will disrupt our
business.
>> Oh, are you are you already in the
process of doing that?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. We invested in multiple
decks, multiple decks per uh
>> So, Crash, how about that right there?
He says that decentralized exchanges are
going to be bigger than centralized
exchanges in the future. What's your
take away from that video?
Yeah. Well, that's why I said in the
tweet that if you had just got done
finishing that video, you might not even
think $100 is crazy because I think
flipping BNB
would put it at $100 for the circulating
market cap. Now, the FTV would be crazy.
It would be like 700 billion. But
considering that crypto is at like 4
trillion market cap, it goes to 10
trillion plus with time. The industry
creeps uh keeps growing. volume keeps
growing over time, more money just keeps
coming into the industry. Um, you know,
BNB right now is 140 billion market cap.
So, is it crazy to think that there, you
know, the number one exchange in the
world would be a 700 billion fully
diluted valuation? At some point, it's
still a little out there, but at the end
of the day, like we have a lot of
companies like what four or five plus
companies above a trillion market cap
now today. I think might be more now.
Tesla.
>> And so being the biggest crypto exchange
in the world, there's a case to be made
that that could possibly be
nearing a trillion dollar valuation at
some point in the future when the
industry expands. But um obviously like
he he said, you know, the DEX would need
to get bigger than the centralized
exchange, which I think is somewhat
possible because a lot of people don't
want to use ID
>> um and passport to sign up with a
platform.
>> So it's possible.
>> Absolutely. and and
>> we're far from that as of now, but yeah.
>> How do you feel about like the like how
do you personally buy? How do you feel
about these perpetual? Do do you ever
like exchanges do you ever trade with
leverage? Are you more of a spot buyer?
Like what do you personally do? And then
why do you think that this is such a
growing industry? How did a a platform
like Hyperlid go from zero in November
to the number 11th ranked cryptocurrency
valued over $20 billion in 9 months?
>> Yeah. So I think okay this is something
that Hyperlid did really good is they
they made a community for utility or an
exchange token like that. This is one of
the biggest problems that all these VC
backed projects and all these utility
coins have is that they have maybe a
great product maybe a medium product
maybe a [__] product and they have no
community like that. Obviously, that's
where meme coins have a way easier time
is they can get a community more easily.
So, the biggest problem with almost all
these exchange coins and all these
utility coins is they have weak
community. What CZ is doing right now,
bro, I don't think people realize it.
Uh, it's actually a masterpiece in the
making where I got to explain and I'm
going a little bit off of the question
you asked because it takes time to
answer this, but basically, how do you
have a really good exchange or utility
coin with a really strong community?
Because typically,
>> once again, you have one or the other.
You don't have both. So, Hyperlid did
really good on actually building a
strong community with the platform
that's going to back it for years and
years to come, hopefully. Whereas I
think CZ and Binance is doing that even
to the next level right now. And I don't
think a lot of people realize. Listen to
this. So let's assume they started with
92% supply control like I've seen. Maybe
who knows maybe 99%. That's what I would
hope honestly. But this what I've
learned from coins is they cannot go up
too fast off of the initial hype. If a
coin goes up way too fast off the
initial hype, then it becomes extremely
hard to go back up because there's gonna
be all these unrealized profits and all
these people that got teleported to a
ridiculous gain so fast. So, let's say a
guy's 1 million just turned into 10
million overnight. It's so hard to
combat all that selling pressure. And so
right now what I think people should
expect is more of like a gradual
incline, a gradual increase because now
on the dips every time people who are
like on the fence, they're going to
sell. They're going to be like, "Is that
the top? Oh, I'm going to sell." Then
the people who really believe in it,
they're going to have a chance to buy
more. That is so much better than just
teleporting higher. If you teleport
higher, all of a sudden you just
teleported undeserving people to massive
gains who are now going to sell 10 to 20
times more. uh like like instead of a
$200,000 sale, now it's a $4 million
sale on top of your head. That's kind of
what happened with Trumpcoin. And that's
something I learned really well from uh
Tronbullcoin,
right? Tronull was a meme on Tron that I
thought was going to do extremely well.
And it popped off to 330 million market
cap. And that was actually a big
downside that I learned from is that
there was too much hype too fast. It
pumps too fast. And now, for example, my
closest followers and community like
they're they're having to FOMO in above
150 million, 200 million, 250 million on
the first day of the of the coin really
being known. And that's a big problem
because these core community people,
they should have had a great entry at 10
million, 15 million, 20 million, 25
million. Now, instead, if any at the
slightest bit of profit taking, the core
community who had to enter higher is now
in a loss. now they have to lose. Now
they're on edge and instead of being
happy, they they're thinking about
selling for a loss. So you don't want to
teleport so fast that a lot of the core
community ends up actually being
underwater and on edge. You actually
want the core community to be in profit
because those are going to be the people
that are happy, excited for the
platform, going to back you. Uh and
especially you'll notice like whenever
you make some people money, they really
love you or they really back you up. So,
like a lot of people back up CZ for that
reason, you know,
>> and and honestly, you probably you
probably feel that way as well. You've
made a lot of people money with a lot of
your calls. I know you you've made me a
lot of money with a lot of your calls
and that's why I mean that's not the
only reason I like you. I think that
you're also a good guy, like a nice guy.
Um, but you know, you probably
experienced that as well. But CZ also
feels that, right? I mean, his token
just hit $1,000. He did a 10,000x. Can I
ask you about this tweet that he posted
and I want to see what you kind of what
you picked up from it. Let's see if we
still have it here. Yep, I got it right
here. Crash. So, CZ Binance posted this
after B&B hit $1,000 per token. He said,
"Watching B&B go from 10 cent ICO price
8 years ago to today's $1,000 is
something words cannot explain." The
last sentence, he says, "This is just
the beginning to the next 10,000x
together. I try to crunch numbers crash.
Another 10,000x from B&B. My phone
wouldn't even do it." Do you think he's
talking about BNB here or do you think
he could be talking about another token
like Aster being the next 10,000X
together?
>> Yeah. No, at this point it can't be BNB.
>> That would like flip
>> that would flip.
>> Yeah, it would flip everything in the
world at that point.
>> So, I think he's probably talking about
Aster and probably from like the first
second of the candle to count it as,
>> you know, who knows.
I mean, it was two cents, you know. It
was two cents. Uh, when did you get your
entry? It was It was
>> Yeah. 35 cents was my very first entry.
34 and a half, 35, and then I just kept
buying buying 36, 37, 38, 39, 40. So, I
got all my major entries filled under
40. So, I'm pretty happy about that.
>> Right around the same. I uh So, I'll
tell you my I don't think I even told
you this. I I first saw CZ Binance's
tweet and I was like just so focused on
the the Fed chair meeting which was
stupid in you know hindsight like who
cares he's going to cut the rates we
already knew it and then I was on a call
and I saw Money Lord say CZ Binance
never shills a tw a ticker I'm putting a
million dollars in and like I had I have
a flashback because Money Lord he's made
a lot of money he put like 10 million
into Trump when it launched and like had
a a total you know he had like over 100
million at one time in Trump token so
that was kind of like my red light that
was around 23 cents and then when I saw
you start posting it. I was like, "Fuck
it." I went in my room. I was like on
Twitter, I saw you post it. I just went
right out to my laptop and I I aped in.
And uh so right around the same time,
like 404 cents. And I mean, where do you
where do you think this thing could go?
We're so early. We do have examples
though, right? Like we can look at what
Hyperlid has done in the space. And then
you can also look at who's building it.
Binance. Uh CZ Binance. They own
everything. They have the number one
exchange. They own Coin Market Cap. They
own Trust Wallet. They own Safe Pal.
They own Pancake Swap. Now they're
building a decentralized exchange.
Everything that they do is the best in
the world. How I mean sitting here
today, it's so early. We're only on day
two and a half crash. It's not it hasn't
even hit a dollar yet. Where do you
think this thing could potentially go?
>> Yeah. So the very first like
super super obvious target is it's going
to get to at least half of hype. Like
there's not to me there's not a question
if that happens. It's going to happen.
Um, and so Hyperliquid right now is at
18.7 billion circulating market cap. So
let's see, uh, last I checked, it's been
a minute. Astra market cap is at 1.4
billion. So to get to half of
Hyperliquid market cap, we're about 8x
away. Uh, and that would put us around
seven bucks. So I I think the first like
maybe they they we'll see a pull back at
like four bucks down to like three or
two bucks before we see probably seven
bucks or not probably see seven. I think
seven bucks is extremely likely. Why?
Once again guys I'm just going based off
of half of Hyperlid. You know you can't
sit there and be like oh you said $7 and
it hits like $630 and be pissed off of
me. Like I'm just going based off my
logic. Hey Hyperlid's at you know$18
billion. we were going to hit half of
that. It makes sense to me. If it makes
sense to you, that's probably what you
will think the the minimum target is.
But the thing is, it has an advantage
over Hyperlid, a big one, which is the
dark pool. And two, it has the Binance
behind it, which whoever's behind
Hyperlid, by the way, and I know I make
jokes calling like Hyper Virgins and
stuff, but whoever's behind Hyperlid is
a beast. Like, I'm super impressed with
Hyperlid and everything they've done in
such a short time frame. Um, but
whoever's behind it is not Binance.
Binance owns Binance. Binance owns Coin
Market Cap and so many other like media
outlets. Like they control crypto media
to a large extent and like I mean
automatically just Binance and Coin
Market Cap that's already like prime
crypto real estate. You know what I
mean? Like they control that,
>> right? I mean
>> Pancake Swap. Yeah.
>> I use the same pal. That's my hardware
wallet. Trust wallet I've used a lot.
Yeah, as well it's good.
>> For me, their new meme platform kind of
like a pump fund on on Binance. Like
they they do it all, man. They are they
are the entity in crypto in my opinion.
>> Yeah, it's it's the biggest in the
world. So, like I said, despite, you
know, I I tip my hat off to whoever's
behind Hyperlid, Jeff, I believe is his
name. Like, it's amazing what they've
done, but I don't care who's behind
whatever platform. It's still not the
same as you pick. Who do you want
backing it? You want Binance and CZ
backing or you want whoever's behind
Hyperlid backing it? I'm taking Binance
and CZ every day behind whatever I'm
doing a good job. You know, Hyperlid has
I mean, they literally have done it
perfectly. But just because you're first
doesn't mean that you're always going to
end up the best, right? I mean, there
has I think there was electric car
companies before Elon Musk came in and
made Tesla. Now, who's the best? It's
Tesla, right? So, I agree with you right
there. It's like I'm I'm backing CZ all
day. It looks like he's going all in.
There's been like three or four tweets
now, Crash, in the past three days where
CZ has mentioned Aster. Let me see if I
can actually pull these up here. So,
>> I saw Yeah. All of them.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, I mean like it's it's
kind of insane. I mean, so CZ Binance
10.1 million followers here online. And
if you notice here too, this used to say
XBinance until the day of him making
that Astra tweet. Now it says at
Binance. I'm like, is he back? Uh, but
for those that don't know, if you go to
Astra's Twitter account, and we'll do it
in just a second, it says backed by YZI
Labs, look who's in CZ Binance's
profile, YZI Labs. But this was the
tweet here. He says, Aster becomes the
biggest BSC USDT holder apart from
Binance Hot Wallet according to Arkham.
You can see Aster on day two and a half
crash owns a holds $131 million
in USDT. I mean, it's insane. And that's
why that that's why that backing by
Binance is so big because no one else in
the world I don't even think Coinbase or
anyone else Michael Sailor could pull
those numbers 131 millions in in two and
a half days.
>> Yeah. I mean it's a lot of USDT. Also
you got to keep in mind that USDT it
shows there well a lot of the USDT like
for example the USDT I put into there I
already swapped it for Aster, right? So
actually those numbers would be a lot
higher I think.
probably double or triple or maybe even
quadruple.
>> You're absolutely right. It's not
counting in all the uh
>> I think probably there's been at least
$400 million of buying demand on Aster
so far. So I would say that's how much
has been converted from USDT into it.
>> Absolutely.
>> You know I think in total there's been
like probably over a billion in volume
since launch. So let's say 400 to 600
million is buy pressure. Now, that's
that's crazy. Remind me to come back to
the fees because I I want to talk about
fees and how they could potentially buy
back the token. But first, I want to go
through the 48 hour stats because they
are very very impressive. So, first 48
hour stats, 2 million users on the
decentralized exchange. 1.3 billion to
uh dollar token all-time high, which
we're at a $ 1.5 billion mark cap right
now. So, that is no longer true. Uh
let's see where that is.
520 billion total trading volume. CZ
Binance publicly supporting. listed on
Binance Alpha and Binance Futures and it
was also listed on MEXC Gate, HTX,
BitMart, and XT listings. So, it has
five different exchanges as of day two
crash. What are your thoughts on CZ
Binance when they decided to only list
this on Astra Dex from the start? You
had to go in there, you had to put money
into their decentralized exchange, you
had to create an account or, you know,
connect your wallet. What are your
thoughts? Do you think that maybe you
think it was perfect how they did it or
do you think maybe they should have
gotten exchange listings in the first 24
hours cuz they are Binance. They could
have went live on Binance on day one.
>> Yeah, they could have got every single
exchange to list it from the very first
second of the launch and that would have
been such a stupid move actually. And I
see a lot of coins have done that in the
past actually that have like a lot of
pool and cuz now think about it. Now
people can say, "Oh, but there's no
Binance listing yet. There's still no
OKX. There's still no Robin Hood.
There's still no Coinbase." So, Binance
is literally putting people in a
position to frontr run all the big
listings. They get to brag about that
like, hey, we prioritize the community
first. We, you know, we fully put the
community first. And they they literally
are, right? So, you know, now you
probably have at least a million people
in before the centralized exchange uh
listings, you know, so those people feel
prioritized and good. Like, this is what
I love, bro, that people don't realize.
Once again, the biggest problem utility
coins and and these exchange coins have
is no community. This is going to have
by far the biggest community of any like
exchange or utility coin we've ever
seen. And by the way, because hype went
first, so many more people now
understood this trade. If if Binance
actually went first, way less people
would have understood this or had
urgency. But it's because people can
compare this to Hype and they saw what
Hype did. Now they're like, "Okay, [__]
this is like I'm really I understand it
this time. And so I think Hyperlid
already had a really great community and
now I feel like Binance is just going to
have like double or triple quadruple
that possibly actually.
>> I like that which is insane.
>> You explained it earlier too because you
know we're we're in on the ground floor
like CZ really did give us a chance. He
could have went live on Binance on
everything day one. And I thought it's
interesting too. I mean, you're
obviously very intelligent in the space
because you understand like how they're
probably doing it cuz when you look at
the chart, you're like, they don't want
it to run too quickly. It kind of did
take off and they even waited. I mean,
CZ could have tweeted about it here.
They waited till 17 cents, shot up to 47
cents and since then it's been like a
slow steady climb. Uh, and it's been
very very impressive. But, you know,
from 0 to $ 1.5 billion market cap in
three days is it it is pretty much
unheard of. Now, I want to come back to
the fees. You said that they've done an
insane amount of of volume obviously on
this token. Do you think that any
portion of those fees is going to go
back into buying back Aster or doing
anything for the
>> It already says somewhere on the site
that there will be fees going uh to
buying back, but not even if it didn't
even say that. First off, it absolutely
will because basically you already know
what the Hyper Virgins are going to say.
They're going to be like, "Well,
Hyperlquid puts 99% of the fees back to
the platform. Therefore, it actually
cares about the platform. It actually
gives back to the community." So,
they're kind of in a spot in my opinion
where Binance has to uh buy back. And
that's anyways, that's the whole model
that everyone likes right now. And it's
the model that makes the most sense. Uh
because for example, if you generate
$150 million of buyback pressure a year,
well, automatically you should be
trading at a multiple of the buyback
pressure, you know, and it helps it feel
a lot safer and it automatically gives
you a massive edge over most coins
because most coins don't have that
ridiculous buyback pressure on top of
it. they're just, hey, someone's selling
or someone's buying, but nobody's buying
and burning like that, uh, or committing
to it like that. So, you just see a lot
more inflows than a typical like, let's
say, net neutral coin, you know.
>> Absolutely. And this was an interesting
tweet. Uh, is his name Kase? Kase Foy.
>> Kase.
>> He's the one that that showed you about
it. I just I don't know why I've never
connected with him. I just followed him
online. Uh, but this was a tweet that he
put up and I want to understand your
thoughts on this because I mean we see
it right now and I've been there before
too, right? Like let's say I got into
Hyperlid early. I own a lot and I see a
competitor come out. It's the natural
reaction for most people to FUD it right
and say, "Oh, this is the T-Moon
knockoff CZ blah blah blah." Like
everything that we saw, we saw millions
of messages. uh he actually posted uh
some screenshots here of a hyperlquid
whale who has $300 million in hyperlquid
buying $10 million of Aster every hour
uh that was going on. So obviously we
saw and usually like hate and FUD rises
loudest. We saw a lot of people hating
on Aster from the start. Do you think
there was a lot of people who got into
Hyperlid pretty early that are whales in
that platform that were actually like
okay kind of seeing the same conviction
that we saw?
I think some of them were biased
probably. Of course, it's easy to get
attached to what's made you a lot of
money, you know, and defend that thing.
It's a pretty natural thing. But also, a
lot of those people are pretty smart.
So, I think when you see Aster trading
at 120th of the market cap of hype, like
anyone with any ounce of logic left in
their brain, buy some. You know, it's
pretty obvious trade, you know.
I think so. Yeah. I I
>> So, I mean, that's what you see with
that will there swapping the $300
million
swapping 10 million in at a time.
>> That's crazy. This breakdown right here
is is you're right because the upside's
so much higher, but it's like BNB 138
billion. Hype 20 billion. Astra as at 1
billion. It's extremely undervalued. And
at the time of at the time of streaming
this right now, Astra is up to 91 cents.
uh listed on Binance Futures, listed on
Binance Alpha. I think a spot listing on
Binance is 1,00% guaranteed. When do you
think that could happen? You think you
think it's better like if you were the
team, is it better to wait a little bit?
Is it better to get other exchanges,
maybe some smaller ones before going
live on on Binance? Like what do you
think the perfect strategy to roll out a
Binance listing would be?
Yeah, I think I was reading somewhere,
but I'm pretty sure their plan is like
past October 1st for that listing on
Binance. I somewhere I don't know why I
think that I saw I don't know if it was
maybe it was the withdrawals of the the
asset or
>> so I'll tell you I'll tell you what it
was cuz I was like dude I was deep in
the trenches these days. So, there was
someone from the Aster team that said,
"Nope, can only buy it on Astro Dex till
October 1st and then the Binance wallet
team. They they put out a tweet because
and I have it right here. I'll pull it
up." Yeah, it's right here. So, this was
the it was from the Binance wallet
account and they were saying updates on
the and maybe you can explain this. The
Binance Alpha token uh migrated into the
Aster token, but you can see the
original plan was to suspend on October
1st, but then they suspended it one day
after launch probably because it went so
well. So, there was a plan to not have
any exchange listings till October 1st,
but maybe it just went so good. I mean,
it went on Binance Alpha, Binance
Futures, and five other exchanges
earlier this morning.
Yeah, I kind of wish that there was no
exchange listings besides
uh just the Astradex,
but I'm thinking that maybe because the
volume was so high, let's say, for
example, it's showing 600 million. Well,
they probably didn't want it to start
showing like 300 million the next day,
then 150 million the day after and 100
million the day after. And they probably
didn't want people to see or think that
volume is going down and therefore it's
losing traction and kind of lose the
heat of the moment. And that's probably
my guess why they decided, okay, [__]
it. Let's just get some smaller
exchanges because it's easier it's
easier to wash trade on these other
centralized exchanges to show and
generate that uh volume to show people.
So at least if they can keep the volume
more constant like hey it was 600
million day one and it's still 600
million in the following days then
people feel like okay man it's still at
the same level of traction and they can
keep that going until they feel ready to
list it um October 1st or sometime in
October but maybe they're just going to
say screw it let's just list it sooner
than on Binance but I think it's a
pretty smart strategy to hold off on
that for now. Yeah, I agree. Look at
this. From zero to the top 66 rank
cryptocurrency at a 1.5, we saw earlier
today $ 1.5 billion mark cap and you
mentioned the volume 616 million which
is very very incredible. Uh let let's
talk about this and whenever you have to
go let me know. Um but I do want to just
>> pretty good right now.
>> Okay, cool. Uh so let's just break it
down, man. There's first off there's so
many people and for me as well and look
I've never traded with leverage. I just
I like to buy crypto at the bottoms.
Like in 2022, I bought all my Bitcoin,
XRP, ETH, Soul, and now I'm taking
profits, right? That's how I like to
trade. It's the easiest, but obviously
you can make a lot of money with
leverage trading. Let's break it down.
Do you recommend it to anyone? Uh, you
know, obviously so many people are doing
it with Hyperlid, but if I'm coming to
Asterex and I want to leverage trade, I
mean, why is this so big? I mean, people
can make multiples. like can you explain
to someone that's watching this why you
would want to do something with 10 20 30
40x leverage?
>> Okay, so let's say you only have $1,000.
>> Can you buy one Bitcoin? No, you can get
01 almost. So if someone has a,000 bucks
and they use a 100x leverage, now they
basically have one Bitcoin on leverage.
So if the price goes up $10,000, now
they'll make $10,000. Whereas if the
price only went up $10,000 before and
they only owned 1% of a Bitcoin, they're
making like what? 100 bucks. So 100
bucks in the case that you only own it.
And then 10,000 bucks if you used 100x
leverage. So obviously, especially the
smaller amount of money you have, I feel
like the more people want to use
leverage cuz they want to make their way
up faster.
But I mean, I I feel like the more money
you get, the less leverage you should
use or need. And like me, for example,
dude, I never keep more than 200 250k in
my leverage account. And then from that,
I can run it up to a million plus. And
then what I do, I take out my profit. I
keep my 200kish in there. Cuz me, man, I
have a bad habit. If I keep my money in
my leverage account, I'll get aggressive
and I'll freaking blow 1.5 million into
500K like like nothing.
>> How quickly,
>> you know? Yeah. So, that's why that's
what I do. Some people are good little
Tinkerbells. They, you know, they'll put
a million in their account and they'll
only risk 10,000. Me, I'm I'm a simple
guy. Whatever's in my account, I just
use it. That's just me, you know. So
that's why me like I never like to put
more than 200 250k in my account
usually. Um and that's how I do it. So
>> very nice. So I mean it makes sense but
yeah it's almost like reverse. It's like
the little guys who are trying to make
money shouldn't be doing it. I've just
seen too many horror stories. I mean
maybe I can get into it. I have an
Asterex account now. Maybe I tried. But
whatever I've been doing has been
working for me. You know just simple
less stress. Obviously, you have the
chance to make more money if you really
have like a a good pulse on the market.
And that's that's why I think that these
dark pools are so big. Maybe we can
explain that next because this is
something new that Binance and and
Asterex are offering. Uh but C maybe you
can talk about dark pools and and why
this actually is going to attract so
many different leverage traders to the
platform.
I mean, obviously I heard about you
talking about it earlier, but people can
kind of avoid feeling targeted or like
people are spying on their warders or
spying on their positions so much. So,
obviously, privacy, if you can have it,
is a nice bonus and that automatically
gives it a huge edge against other
platforms. So, that's an obvious bonus.
>> Yeah.
>> Also, let's say someone put in a limit
order to buy a billion dollar at a
$100,000 Bitcoin price. Well, now
everyone's just going to, you know, bid
it right above their their limit order,
right? They're going to frontr run that
big ass limit order. So now people can
literally just I don't know h if someone
would really put a billion dollars in a
single limit order like that, you know,
but
>> big limit orders can be set and not
everyone's just going to go put a
freaking order right above your your
limit order like that. So that
automatically should attract way more
volume and and uh usage than a lot of
other platforms. That probably
automatically alone gives it like a
extra 30 to 50% volume than uh than it
probably would have without that feature
which is huge because that makes it that
makes a massive difference in volume.
That's the difference between uh on a
trillion dollars of volume. Well, now
you have $1.5 trillion in volume over
time just because that one feature, you
know, so it makes a big difference.
>> It's a huge feature. feel like the space
is kind of moving that way. I know
you're a big fan of Monero as well and a
lot of people have been talking about
Monero. I bought a lot of Monero. Uh
just that privacy aspect, right? And
this is obviously it's different, right?
Like on on if you trade Ethereum, people
can track your trades, track your
wallet. It's okay. It has some benefits.
It doesn't. But I think this actually is
important too. And I think the guy I was
talking about is James Whim. He was
doing hundred million dollar leverage
trades. And you know, even though like
right after, let's say he put placed a
long on the market, the markets would
dump for like a couple hours and then
they would send. And it's like I was
just like, damn. I feel like there's
some massive manipulation here. And it
probably I think Justin Sun Justin Sun
literally made a tweet like, "Who wants
to put money together to hunt this guy?"
Didn't he? Or was it Justin Sun or maybe
it was someone else? So like, and then
they got him, you know, shortly after.
So
>> it's insane. They got him. I mean a lot
of times he lost I think he had like 50
60 million. So that was one of the
stories I was like I'll stay away from
this um for the time being but yeah as
of now aster up to 87
>> almost broke the $1 mark. It's been on
absolute rise since it went live. CZ
Binance tweeted about it. So many people
are getting into the community. Uh
you've probably noticed it as well. I
mean, it's it's people from all
different walks of life, all different
places, getting in at all different
entries that are rallying behind this.
And you mentioned that Binance did this
the right way by launching this and kind
of getting in people first to hold the
ground floor. And you're right when you
were talking, I'm like, "Oh, I feel that
way." Like I feel like I did get
somewhat of an early entry before it
goes live on exchanges like Coinbase,
Binance, etc. Um, and that's what they
did. They they built a good community.
But the amount of people that are
talking about it, I I put out a tweet
saying that I haven't seen
a token have this much mind share on X?
And I don't know if it was just popping
up in my algorithm. I don't know about
people in the chat if they felt this way
as well, but every tweet I saw crash was
about Aster. I said, I haven't seen this
since Pepe back in 2023. And you
probably remember that. I mean like
everybody was tweeting about Pepe, you
wake up. It's like Pepe listed on
Kraken, Gemini, Cuccoin Daily making
videos. I feel like I haven't seen I
mean realistically this much mind share
and this this many people talking about
Astra whether good or bad since
something like Pepe went live back in
2023.
>> Yeah. And Pepe went to 11 billion. Astra
is like 1.4 billion.
>> Now love Pepe amazing
>> top memecoin but Pepe is not going to
generate you know tens of millions of
dollars in fees monthly in the future
like this probably will. So it's a big
difference in just automatic buy
pressure that uh this will have over
time. So you know I which has a higher
ceiling longterm probably a but you know
the platform does need to succeed like
and be like fully fully established
locked and loaded which I mean look it's
not like it's a random guy trying to do
this. It's Binance behind it. They run
the biggest exchange in the world.
someone knows how to make a successful
exchange, I think it's them. So, the
chances are pretty damn high that it's
going to be a very successful exchange.
I can't really understand betting
against the richest exchange in the
world. It just doesn't make sense to me,
you know, which is what some people are
doing,
>> especially when he comes out and says
decentralized exchanges are going to be
bigger than centralized exchanges like
like told us uh exactly what he was
thinking and then he goes out and builds
it. Um, I agree with you, man. I think
it's going to be massive. I I mean,
we're only on day two and a half. So,
what's your thoughts on top blasting,
right? Because I did it, you did it
yesterday, right? We both top blasted
yesterday or two days ago, maybe it was.
I don't I think it was two days ago. Uh
but the chart like I'll pull it up now
because when I top when when we both
bought in, we bought in right around the
same time.
>> It was like right here. Like maybe we
caught this dip, but it was all-time
highs. We top blasted to anyone that's,
you know, like watching it today. 87
cents. It's like it obviously it's not
financial advice. This is just you
telling what you would do for yourself
like today. Do you top blast here? Do
you wait for a better entry for people
that are sideline? Like what what what's
something that Crashers Clay would do
with this token?
>> Yeah. When in doubt, sell half, keep
half. Or in this case, when you're
trying to get in, when in doubt, buy
half, keep half on the, you know, ready.
That's what I always do whenever I'm in
doubt. If I'm ever in a position that's
too big, that keeps me up at night. If
I'm ever in a position that has me
nervous, I I'm just like, "Hey, what am
I doing? Why am I feeling nervous? Stop.
Cut half of it." And I keep half and I
can add the other half back on later
when I feel more comfortable. Or guess
what? If I never have to add the second
half back on, that means the trade just
went incredibly well and just [__]
blasted off, right? And okay, great.
Fine. I won. Like, you know, never even
had to add the second half. That's
pretty cool. Like, too, you know,
>> that's that's super smart. I like that.
Sell half, keep half. Right now, Aster
is at 87. Have you sold half or you
keeping the whole 100%.
>> I'm keeping 100% for now. Like, I'm up
more than double and I could sell half
keep half, but I don't have like I'm
sleeping at night super good. Like I
don't I don't feel nothing like I said
cuz for me like for why can I top blast
at 35 to 40 cents? Because at the time
it's only 120th the market cap of hype.
So, in my head, I have a very strong
confidence that it's gonna have to at
least get to one half of hype. And I
think that's pretty much the worst case
scenario because there's a very strong
case to be made that this flips hype
because it has Binance behind it. Has a
$80 billion net worth man behind it. It
has the number one centralized exchange
in the world behind it and their
exchange Binance prints like what how
much money do they make profit? Like
over a billion dollars a year, I think,
right? So why why would I fade those
pockets and how deep that money goes? It
just doesn't make sense. There's a
stronger case to be made that the team
and whoever's behind Binance is stronger
than who's even behind Hyperlquin. And
there's an incredible team behind
Hyperlid, you know. So that's why like,
bro, I'll sleep on it. And here's the
thing, I can live with my decision. If
this [__] drop to 30 cents tomorrow and
I round trip, I'm up like around 1.6
$1.8 million in the last 30 hours on
this, right? If I round trip that,
>> I will live with the result. Why?
Because my logic is strong in my mind on
why this should minimum get to one half
of hype. And that's and that's the worst
case to me. So I live with my decisions.
If I round trip, it's on me. But
whenever it gets to half of hype at
least, that's on me as well. I'll
happily take some gains maybe off the
table then. You know, at that point, I
should be up what 8 to 9 to 10x. So, at
that point, it's really easy to take 20%
off, 50% off, and still have a massive
position running, you know? So, that's
that's my logic. Now, there's a lot of
people in this space, you know, they
love to [__] on you when something comes
back down. But the whole reason they
held is why cuz they thought it was
going to go higher, too. So, you you
idiot. You know, you held cuz you
thought it was going to go higher.
That's exactly what I'm doing, too.
Sometimes it's going to pay off.
Sometimes it's not. At the end of the
day, what do you sleep sound with at
night knowing that that's what you
believe in? That's that that is what you
think is the best decision. I think the
best decision right now is not to sell
even half, not even to sell a quarter.
I'm sleeping good on my position until
minimum I think half of hype, you know.
>> Wow.
>> I like that. And uh real quick on that
revenue, you you said maybe it's a
billion. It's Binance's revenue for 2024
was reported at 16.8
billion. I'll pull up their uh exchange
in just a second. Here is Hyperlquid as
you mentioned 18.73
billion market cap. 17.4 uh uh 56 FDV
and doing $310 million in value. So
Crash is saying maybe around that 9
billion mark is when he's going to
consider taking profits. I think we're
at a $ 1.5 billion today. I'm like I
don't know. I I think I'm with you. I'm
betting on CZ and I'm I'm betting on uh
Aster and I think that you know they're
the number one for everything else and
there's no world there like if we live
in a simulation there's no world that
they aren't the number one decentralized
exchange by a long shot. That's kind of
what I'm betting on and I yeah I have
conviction I would sleep well at night
if I didn't sell. So I might listen to
you. You're much smarter when it comes
to this than me. Uh my buddy Mike Farley
says I might not ever sell. Uh you're
much smarter than this when it comes to
me. But I I think that, you know, I
think that we're going to see this thing
do incredible numbers. Now, I do also,
while you're here, want to transition
away from Aster and B&B and talk a
little bit about Brett on base as well
as that base airdrop. I saw you post
about that. Can you give us the update
on Brett trading well over $500 million
mark cap today, top meme coin in the
world, and also that base airdrop. How
cool is that?
Yeah, I mean anyone who watched my
original videos on Brett, it was
actually centered the thesis largely
around, hey, bass is going to do a
airdrop at some point. But then later
down the line, Bass said we're not going
to do an airdrop. And so both were
really positive actually because I I
mean from the beginning though it was
base airdrop. Once once they said no no
no base coin I was just like well [__]
since there's no base coin Brett is the
base coin basically because it's the
biggest coin in the
>> entire better narrative.
>> It's not better. I actually think the
airdrop is better. Um but I I think the
airdrop is a lot better. That's the
original vision of Brett in my opinion.
Uh well not in my opinion like factually
like if you go back to my videos that's
the original vision. So you know we just
made a pivot once they said there's not
going to be a basecoin. It just kind of
was like logical like, "Okay, well then
I guess Brett's the biggest coin on this
chain, so cool. Brett's the base coin
then." But no, dude, the airdrop is
crazy because right now in memes, we're
lacking a lot of fresh new demand in
memes right now. Like most people are
down bad in memes and they just want one
more pump. So like in 2021, we went so
high with the stimulus checks. That's
what a base airdrop is, is a stimulus
check directly on base. And what most
people are going to do when they get
that stimulus check of 1,000 to 5,000 to
10,000 with some even larger wallets and
whales probably going to get up to
$50,000 in airdrop. Bro, it's insane how
much money is going to find its way into
into Brett because at the end of the day
in 2021
during the craze of the the bull run
what percentage of transactions do you
think on Ethereum were towards buying
SHIB? You know, you know, obviously
NFTTS made up a big percentage of
transactions, but I just want to hear
what do you think?
>> What is the percentage of transactions
probably going towards SHIB on ETH in
2021?
>> It's got to be like I mean 10% sounds
like a lot, but I mean it went to what
$42 billion mark cap. Everyone was
buying it.
>> Everyone was buying. I mean, a a soccer
mom, you know, after a day of work.
Well, no, soccer mom is not even
working. She's dropping her kids off at
the games. But
>> a soccer mom that's buying shib,
>> I mean, do you think
>> uh she's buying like some DeFi protocol
on on ETH? No, I don't think so. I think
she's buying SHIB. Like I heard soccer
moms talking about ship. Like that's
what I remember. That's why I bring up
soccer mom,
>> you know. So when you get to the point
of soccer moms are buying it, kids in
high school are buying it. [__] even
kids in middle school are buying it.
Like I think it's pretty fair to say
that's at least 20% of transactions on
chain. Like that's hands down in my
opinion. Like when Trump happened, what
is everyone doing? Everyone like at
least 40% of transactions on chain are
towards Trump, right? And SHIB, I'm not
talking about all the time, right? I'm
talking about in the peak moments, in
these beautiful moments where like just
all this extra money, right? Trump, 40%
of transactions at least are going
towards Trump. Uh on SHIB, bro, I I
would say in the peak of that, at least
40% of transactions on ETH were going
towards SHIB. So now you take 40% of the
airdrop. We can even lower it down to
20%.
But let's say I mean on base they say
there's around what? 18 million wallets.
20 million wallets. So, let's say about
5% of those wallets get a airdrop
between $1,000 and $50,000.
Let's say the average uh airdrop for
someone, remember, it could be between
$1,000 $5,000. So, let's go on the lower
end, though, cuz I always want to use
low numbers for these speculative
projections. Say the average airdrop is
2500 bucks. Okay, so once again, there's
18 million wallets. About 5% of them get
it. So let's say about a million wallets
get on average 2500 bucks. Take 2500
bucks times a million wallets and now
that's $2.5 billion of fresh new
liquidity. Keyword new liquidity, right?
Not like, hey, I got to go sell this
other coin to buy. Uh, no, it's I'm
selling this free money that I just got
to now I can take that and buy the next
thing with that. Cuz that's what people
do when they get airdrops. They're never
just satisfied. No one ever got a
airdrop and was just like I mean like
90% of people they were not they don't
just get the airdrop and be like okay
thanks for the free money I'm out of
here I'm out of the casino I'm I'm done
with crypto. No like everyone takes the
airdrop and they throw it to the next
thing. So you take 40% of $2.5 billion
of fresh liquidity and you have over a
billion dollars in demand on a Brett.
Okay, over a billion dollars in demand
on a 500 million market cap coin. Well,
go on a little uh coin right now that's
like a $100,000 market cap. Put $1,000
into it and you'll see the market cap's
going to rise by like at least 10,000
market cap, right?
>> So, let's say every $1,000 you put in,
the market cap goes up 10,000. So, now
it's basically at a 10x multiple of what
you put in. So, you put a billion
dollars in, the market cap just went up
basically 10 billion. You see, that's
how Brett gets past 10 billion with
those low projections of the average
airdrop being about 2500 bucks.
>> You know, the numbers are simple, bro.
Like, if you just if you actually just
use a little bit of logic and think
about it, and I'm going with low
numbers.
>> I'm going with low estimations. This is
going to be the biggest airdrop ever in
crypto, bro. So, remember, I freaking
planned this out 18 months ago. Anyone
can go back watch my original YouTube
videos when I broke this down. So like,
bro, I've been ahead on this for a long
time. It's just that base then said
we're not doing a basecoin and then they
flipped back and said they are doing it.
So Trump won and I think a lot of people
got a little bit more like uh lenient, I
guess. But I mean, dude, this is going
to be a ma this is probably going to be
the biggest airdrop in history. We see
like MetaMask hinting at an airdrop. I
think I saw Trust I saw Trust Wallet
launch a token, but obviously Bass
launching a a token and airdrop is going
to be absolutely massive. It's pretty
much Coinbase's token. That's what we're
looking at, right? It's Coinbase's
native token essentially.
>> Yeah. Take half of Binance coin and you
get the valuation probably give or take
of Coinbasecoin,
>> right? Binance is 140 billion. Take half
of that, you're at a $70 billion market
cap for Basecoin.
And then once again you take 5 to 13% of
that and you arrive to the bre uh market
cap which would be at 13% around 8 to 9
billion. If you do the airdrop
projections you get to past 10 billion.
So that's you know 16 to 20x from
today's entry right now. And that's not
factoring in other positive factors that
can come into play. You know, I mean, we
have the market's pricing in two or
three more rate cuts in the following
months. I saw in Poly market there's
like 86% chance of rate cut next month,
like 75% chance of the month after that,
and I think 65% chance the month after
that. So, there's a lot of positive
factors. And I just want to say by the
way, so you know how a lot of coins or
like companies are announcing they want
to do their token now like MetaMask
um and some other ones Binance now just
dropped this one and there's more like
they're all all of a sudden coming out
and saying we're going to do our token.
Why do you think of all times they
finally decided they're gonna you know
they these guys have been saving their
ability to drop a project for years? You
know they could have done it six months
ago, 12 months ago. Why do you think
they're doing it now?
>> I think it's because they're confident.
>> They're confident, bro, in the outlook
in the coming months. So, they feel like
it won't be wasted because you can only
ever drop a Metamas token once.
>> You know, you do it at a [__] time.
Congratulations. Like, that's just a
waste, you know? I mean, can it be
successful still? Yes. It's just like
you want to maximize that once in a
lifetime thing. Like, you you're only
going to get to launch Metamascoin once.
You're only going to get to launch Aster
once. Why not try to do it at the best
possible time where you're confident in
the future months in the, you know, the
coming outlook. So, I think it's a
really good sign that Coinbase all of a
sudden says they want to do their token.
Binance drops their token. Uh, MetaMask
and other people want to do their token
now of all times. And it's at the time
where altcoins look the mo like altcoins
are so beat up. But and and but to me,
it's like we're at the end of the
tunnel, right? Like we're so close to
being out. So that's just like a clue
that I pick up on. To me, it's not even
a clue. It's like a very obvious, hey,
like look at this. If you have any brain
cells, you should get that, you know.
>> Absolutely. Yeah. I mean, that's that's
kind of what I've been basing my
analysis on as well. It's like a lot of
this plays into the the macro markets as
well. You know, you look at the Dow
Jones, the S&P 500, the Russell 2000 at
or near all-time highs in 2021. The
Russell 2000 was a good indicator of
massive amounts of liquidity coming into
the market once it broke through its
all-time highs. We also saw the altcoin
market go as well. What's your outtake?
Obviously things are different this
year, right? We have a pro crypto
president. We have so much things going
positively for crypto. People say that
every year though, right? They say this
is different. I remember last cycle
we're at $65,000 Bitcoin. Like this is
different. We're going to 100,000 then
200,000. It's a super cycle. What's your
outlook on crypto this cycle? Do you
think that it we're still in this
four-year cycle? I mean, do you think
that we have a couple months left? Like
what's your take and how are you kind of
positioning yourself?
No, I I think the four-year cycle is a
thing of the past right now. When your
grandma gets it, it's outdated
information. It's it's too late. So, I
think that uh you know, the funniest
outcome here is, you know, everyone
expects a top in the coming month or two
based off the four-ear cycle. So, many
people are going to sell early and uh
the the best gains will actually be had
after the typical four-year cycle. So
maybe by December or beginning of the
next year. So that I think that's the
most likely thing right now actually.
>> I like that. And then how how low do you
think we could potentially go? Right.
Like every year we've had an 80% around
that retracement. We last cycle we were
at $69,000 FTX Terral Luna Voyager
Celsius. We went all the way down to
$15,000 Bitcoin. Do you think that I
mean with all the companies and people
that are getting into crypto right and
maybe for the wrong reasons just to make
money? I mean, personally, I think that
we might see a pretty big retracement.
How how big do you think that we go?
Let's say we go up to $150,000 Bitcoin
or don't have to use that, but like do
you think that we kind of still stay on
that 80% retracement for altcoins,
cryptocurrency, Bitcoin?
>> Well, first off, every cycle the crash
has been a little less severe. You know,
the first one's like what 92 95% then it
goes down like 87 83 and the last one's
76%.
So, automatically based on that, you
would think, okay, at least this one,
worst case, 70%. But I don't think it's
going to get to even 70%. Uh, not for a
while. I think there's too many dollars,
too little Bitcoin right now. True.
>> And also, we're closer.
We're less people are believing in the
dollar than ever before. That's a big
difference this cycle than than the
last. So, you know, everyone just looks
at the past. uh but has no vision for
the future. And the fact that, you know,
they are moving stable coins, not not
just stable coins, like they're they're
trying to move everything on chain, it
shows you the direction we're headed.
Once people are on chain, dude, like
come on, bro. More people are going to
be using Bitcoin. More people are then
going to be taxed on every crypto thing
they do. They're going to be surveiled
more on every little thing they do. Uh,
and at that point, bro, a lot less
people will probably want to use the the
dollar uh once they're already on the
blockchain. You know, like everyone
wants and needs the dollar so badly when
that's the only thing that people take.
But once everyone's on chain,
>> I I think like
>> it becomes a lot easier for other things
to to gain way stronger dominance versus
the dollar.
>> I agree 100%. Are you worried at all
about these like massive uh companies
like Michael Sailor and I mean Anthony
Pompiano, Jack Morers, the Trumps, you
know, the Trumps hold a massive amount
of crypto. Like that's one thing that
I'm kind of like, you know, Michael
Sailor, he'll probably never ever he'll
probably go to the grave never selling
his Bitcoin. Pabliano, he's a crypto
guy, but like some of these other people
that are getting in that are holding
masses amounts of crypto, are they do
you think they're going to adopt the
rule number one, never sell your
Bitcoin, or some of these people, they
might be in it to make a lot of money,
they might sell. And also, I am a little
bit worried about these people that hold
massive amounts of of Bitcoin and crypto
and they're issuing stock. It's like
what if something similar to FTX,
Teruna, like some cataclysmic events
happen during the bare market and you
know, there is a chance that these
things do happen.
Yeah, here's the thing, bro. I I never
borrow money in my life besides 200
grand from Kase, actually. Um, so yeah,
I never borrow money ever in my life
besides a little from Kase one time. So
that's the thing, man. My like it would
be so foolish of me to act like
borrowing money and all that [__] is my
expertise cuz I [__] borrowed money
once in my life. So, I don't really know
too much like how bad. I mean, I know,
bro. People get into trouble borrowing
money. So, yeah. I mean, that's a
concern, but also I mean, I don't know.
Here's the way I see it. If there was
only 21 million houses in the world,
would you try to bet on the prices of
those houses going down?
>> No. There's seven.
>> No. Right. Because like
>> Yeah. There's 8 billion people and
everyone needs a house. Well, okay.
Here's the thing. someone gets
liquidated on their Bitcoin. Well, here
here's the thing. Like, there's actually
possibly more pound-for-pound demand for
one Bitcoin than for one house. Now,
that sounds crazy because you would
think, well, everyone wants a house,
right? There's 8 billion people, uh, you
know, and everyone wants a house. So,
how is it possible that there's more
pound-for-pound demand on one Bitcoin?
It's possible, or maybe we're close. I
can't see the exact ratio of that right
now. like there's no chart of that I
don't think or at least if there is I
don't know how to look at that but
here's the thing when Bitcoin you know
people can buy there are people out
there that can buy a th000 Bitcoin
10,000 Bitcoin 20,000 Bitcoin whereas
not everyone wants to buy 10,000 houses
so automatically the amount of Bitcoin
per one person that someone can buy uh I
think is potentially a lot higher rate
there so
>> I I think that There is
if if someone gets liquidated in a
massive way, okay, you lose however many
Bitcoin, but there's just a lot of
people in the world who just like they
would want a house, right? Like let's
say you're homeless cuz there's only 21
million houses. You didn't get a house.
There's so many people that bam
instantly they're just going to buy that
house cuz they need a place to live.
Now, in the case of Bitcoin, you don't
need to live in a Bitcoin, but you have
all these dollars that you want to get
rid of. And I think you will get rid of
them for Bitcoin. Uh when there's so
many dollars, and once again, every year
there's more and more more and more and
more dollars. Same amount of Bitcoin
pretty much. So, I I think we're just at
a point now there's just too many
dollars and too much pound-for-pound
demand for one Bitcoin. Uh, at this
point I I don't maybe I'm naive to think
that, but I I do think that. Once again,
there's just too many dollars in the
world now, bro.
>> It's Yeah. No, I like I like the way
your brain thinks as well. And it just
it just shows the demand for Bitcoin.
How much Bitcoin do you think someone
needs to be extremely well off, like
financially secure? What's like your
number? Like, hey, if and you might be
different than average people. you made
a lot of money in the crypto space, but
like for the average person, like if you
make this if you if you own this these
many bitcoins, this many bitcoins,
you're set for life.
>> Yeah. I I don't know why, but I don't
like the idea of like targeting a
certain amount of Bitcoin and thinking
I'll be set for life because
I feel weird depending on like uh
something that someone else created and
all of a sudden I have all my faith in
this like thing that uh you know someone
else like it just doesn't sit well with
me. Like
>> you become God like that becomes your
God now you know like that's like God.
>> Yeah. You know, I rather have multiple
things. Um,
>> like for for me, the first thing I tell
people, man,
>> is secure your peace as soon as you can.
So, like for you, I don't know what the
little houses that everyone would feel
comfortable in. Some people, they're,
you know, they need a $2 million place
to feel comfortable. But I know me,
like, bro, I just need like a $250,000
place. And maybe to some that's a lot.
Like some people in some countries,
they're like, "Shit, I just need
$120,000 to have a a comfy little spot."
For me, it's like 250k I would need,
right? So, the first thing I would do if
I made $400,000, right? I had a good run
in the market. Bam. Instantly, I take
250k out and I buy that little apartment
or place and I'm living cozy. I don't
have to pay rent. I don't have to worry
about my expenses are not going to be
that big. I just got to buy groceries or
buy some food. I'm going to survive.
Like now I already have way more peace
than owning a certain amount of Bitcoin.
You know, if you own a certain amount of
Bitcoin, that's what you depend on.
Well, now you got to sell that Bitcoin
to pay your rent, to do these things.
And now you see your Bitcoin stack is
getting smaller. That doesn't feel good.
But first thing I do, I buy my place. I
know a lot of people say, "Hey, borrow
money. Uh never, you know, always get a
30-year fixed mortgage. Don't pay in
cash. is stupid because the cost of
borrowing money is cheap enough that you
can just take that money and you can
invest in the market and get a bigger
turn. I don't believe in that. I don't
care what you know people can do what
they want. I rather just own my [__] and
feel comfy at home.
>> Okay, I got some nice lighting around
me. I feel cozy. I'm happy. If I lost
all my crypto right now, bro, I Bro, I
have some salmon in the fridge. I mean,
I can walk down for three bucks outside
the place and I can get myself a awesome
strawberry smoothie. I'm going to
survive.
>> I'm chilling. Yeah, you're chilling.
>> Yeah, I'm chilling. So, and and and you
can buy yourself that piece, you know,
once again, depends on which country
you're in, it could be 120K. And if
you're in, you know, one one country in
the US, maybe the average home is like
$400,000, right? $450. So, it depends.
But first thing I do, man, I make good
money. I buy my place, feel cozy at
home.
>> Then I start building up the safety net
beyond that, which is, okay, is Bitcoin
what gives you comfort? Is that what
makes you feel good at night when you go
to sleep? Okay, start stacking some
Bitcoin. Uh, is there anything else that
makes you feel good? I would start
stacking that, you know, and I just
progress, you know, like that's what I'm
doing, you know. Personally, like I feel
more cozy buying uh Monero than Bitcoin.
So, you know, and here's the thing. I if
Bitcoin just destroyed Monero and Monero
became obsolete, nobody gave a [__]
about it, which I think is like a 0%
chance or like 1% chance. Dude, it's
fine. I rather pursue what I believe in
in my life. Like I rather back the [__]
that I think is the real [__] the good
[__] than back something else because
it's deemed more popular or it's deemed
more conventional or safe. I'm not here
to play safe, bro. I'm here to lose
everything. And if I do, bro, I got my
cozy place with nice lighting and
strawberry smoothies for three bucks.
I'm okay, you know. But that's me. Some
people you rather stack the safe
conventional thing and you do you, you
know, but me, I rather own my place, own
some Monero, and own some other things
that I think can do a lot of multiples.
>> So, for example, Astra is like one of
those things, you know, I'm sleeping
good at night. I feel confident in that.
Brett, right? I feel so confident that
when there's extra money flowing around,
Brett's going to absolutely send and it
can produce a lot more multiples than
for me than Bitcoin. Remember, I own my
place multiple. So, I'm happy, bro. I'm
good. And anyways, I think that's the
best position to put yourself in because
once you feel safe, like whatever you
fall back on, whatever your safety net
is, once you feel safe with that, you
can take big risks and it's actually not
so bad if you fail. you know, like you,
oh [__] you know, you're okay with the
worst case. But when you're not okay
with the worst case and you can't go to
sleep and you feel so [__] about what if
this happens, what if that happens? Like
it's it's just not as good, you know, uh
for me.
>> No, that's it's that's genius right
there, you know, because a lot of people
fall into that ideology. I'm glad I
don't, but it's like only Bitcoin, stack
it all. And it's like for you it's like,
you know, like get your piece get your
peace secured. You made money. You made
half a million dollars in
cryptocurrency. this internet money that
like digital money like go buy a h go
buy whatever you want like take care of
yourself um and that is that is the most
important you know that that's something
that I experienced last cycle from 2021
did you know at the all-time high I
didn't sell I kind of believed in the
ideology that we're going to go up
forever I didn't really start like
taking profits until we went from 4900
down to 3k I took out enough to like
survive right um but I all my crypto I
wrote it all the way down so I was just
holding the whole time and like there is
something with that where it's just a
feeling of uneasiness, right? As opposed
to, yeah,
>> even if I sold ETH at 4,000 on the way
up and like took some profits. Maybe I
didn't hit 4,900, but I could have
secured it, got a nice spot, like did
something well. And that's something
I've done a little bit better uh this
cycle is just taking small profits, you
know, not holding the bag too long. And
um one thing that I I I think is
important too, and I would hate to be a
maxi of anything because you would have
missed this aster trade, right? Like
it's the most obvious trade of 2025 in
my opinion. The Trump trade was one and
this is another one. And if you're just
married to one, and we're seeing with
people that hate Aster, if you're
married to one token and one ideology,
you can never win big. I mean, look, you
you love Brett. You've you've talked
about some other great tokens that are
doing well. But you saw last year, you
and you've been bulling it on your
timeline, you know, pretty much every
day. So, it's like I think people can
learn that from you is that look, people
would associate you with Brett, right?
like you've you've been the face of
Brett, probably one of the most vocal
leaders, but even you are still looking
at
>> people see Brett. What what about before
Brett? What about all the plays before
that? There's, you know, Brett is the
number one meme on base. That play is
going to print, bro. No matter what is
how what is is the number one meme coin
on base not? It's just like what? It's
never going to go up. Come on. That's
stupid. Like when there's extra money
flowing around, people buy memes. People
try to make a multiple. And one of the
biggest magnets that's gonna attract
people isn't leading me on base. Like
it's just obvious. So I sleep at night
so peacefully with that. And that's the
thing, you don't have to only have one
bet. I sleep good at night with that.
I'm now sleeping good at night with
Astra. If another great play comes
around, I'll be happy to take it if it
makes complete and total sense to me.
I'm at a point now where though, like if
something doesn't make complete and
total sense, man, I rather just sit out,
you know? That's why in the last 14
months, I've only made two calls. Tron
bull aster. You know what pissed me off
so much about Tron is it went up 55x
after I called it. And I know that more
people lost than they won. So to me that
was like a big wakeup call of like [__]
I can't just call [__] anymore cuz if it
hits 330 million like it does 55x oh
well it's still considered a loss
because it turns out that a lot of the
people buying up there is the people
from me. like the level of success
something needs to go to for me to be
like, you know, good. It's like too high
almost right now that I I just have to
be so selective. Like, bro, people say
it, uh, you know, if I'm such a scammer,
why didn't I just show you a,000 coins
for $10,000 per coin? I could have made
10 million, 20 million plus dollars just
promoting [__] Instead, I've only
called two things in the last 14 months
because I don't want people to lose
because of me. I understand people will
always lose in crypto. But the main
thing I want the main like 20% of people
that follow me closely that actually
care about what I have to say, I just
want to make sure those people win,
right? Like if those people win, I'm
super happy. But if those people don't
win, what am I doing? I have no reason
to share anything. It's it's too much
pressure. Like I don't want to lead
people to lose. And uh you know there's
no fun in that. What's the point of
leading people to lose? I'd rather just
say nothing, you know.
>> Yeah. I mean, you called a token that
that went from 5 million to $330 million
and you still get called a scammer. This
and that. It's like it's wild. Do you
ever get like tripped out at how big
your platform has become and and how
much pull you have in the crypto space?
I mean, it makes sense cuz like what 10
of my last 11 calls or like 10 of my
last 12 did over 100x. So, it almost
becomes like a self-fulfilling prophecy
at this point, but be because of like
those repeated wins. It didn't used to
be like that. And but here's the thing,
right? So, let's say I go share poop
shitcoin, right? Uh, and let's say some
people just buy it just because of me,
but it's not going to last, right? It's
not going to last. You can't just think,
"Oh, because people think that I'm
always right, then therefore I can call
anything." That's not how it works. Uh,
if the [__] is not solid without you,
you can call it. Maybe shortterm it's
going to get some attention. It will die
out. So I think since the beginning the
most important thing to me has been am I
correct before I ever talk about
something am I correct about it before I
ever even said a word about it if I'm
correct then the following sequence of
events can be good ones that allow it to
you know that can just be complmentary
to it reaching the point that it should
have already without me. So I never want
any coin to depend on me and I felt like
tromble it kind of became like that and
uh you know that really just taught me
like okay this isn't the same as it was
before you know when I was smaller I
could just call anything and you know
it's not like I pushed the price or it's
not like people immediately reacted or
anything and so it made the game a lot
harder and that's why for like 14 months
bro I haven't been able to call [__]
because I haven't seen anything that is
going to expand big enough far beyond my
own audience, right? Capture the mind
share of outside of just my people, like
really burst out of the bubble and go
big enough to where all my followers can
win. So, the game became a lot harder.
And because I can't really call [__]
unless I'm super confident it can make
liquid exes for all the people that
follow me. And like Aster, dude, it's so
liquid.
>> It's got so much volume. It's got, you
know what I mean? Uh that's something
that I can confidently share, you know?
um because of how much money I know is
just look at the volume on that thing.
Look at uh bro Binance the richest
exchange in the world behind that thing.
We got in on day one, you know, like
that's finally there was something that
I felt like, okay, I can actually share
that me and everyone we can make good
X's and it's going to be a good win.
Everyone's going to be happy, you know.
But uh it it does me no good to call a
shitcoin at 5 million, it goes to 100
million. Oh wow, it did 20x. But
supposedly, well, it's my fault that if
it comes down from 100 million because
it only did a 20x, that's the standard
now if it's a less liquid coin. Now, if
Aster goes up 4x, I know everyone's
happy cuz it's super liquid. Everyone
can exit. Everyone can make profit there
like easily, you know, but whenever
there's lower cap memes like that, you
know, it's it's a lot harder.
>> Yeah, I have your first tweet here. Uh,
Aster about to hit alltime high right
now. It's at 92. Alltime high is 924. Uh
this is your first tweet right here.
Crash hype
57 billion FTV. Aster 3.5 billion FTV.
Binance hype. Bet a h bet a house on
aster under 3.5 billion. I think the
what the actual circulated market cap
was probably 400 500 million at the
time.
>> And then
>> who is Yeah. Who is this guy? Aster is
being overvalued. A lot of people don't
even know how to buy. Like that's oh
that's a tough tweet for this person.
Alpha Researcher because this was at
like 30 cents and here we are today
crash at alltime highs at 92 cents right
now.
>> Yeah, that's the thing, dude. Like you
can't go based off of the present. The
market is upon
>> Sorry to interrupt you.
>> The market is built on pricing in the
future, you know? So, if you just look
at the stats today, you're going to get
[__] out of the future.
>> Wow. We're looking at alltime highs live
crash 928.
Uh looking good. I mean, this is a it
really is a once in a-lifetime
opportunity. You know, I not once in a
lifetime, but there's only a couple
times per year that something like this
happens. I feel like Trump was one of
them. There it is. 93 new alltime high
at 93 cents. And uh this one, I mean,
you the last time that we've seen CZ
Binance post a chart, I mean, it's only
been B&B. He's never posted another
token. He posted this uh and yeah, I
mean, it's just been a perfect
opportunity on the decentralized
exchange. We obviously see other tokens
in that same sector, Hyperlquid, doing
insane. We understand some people paint
this as like a revenge story for CZ. I
don't know if I really necessarily
believe that, but it's just a huge
untapped market and Binance is the best
at everything in crypto. It makes sense
that they're going to be the best in
this market as well. It makes perfect
sense to me.
>> Yeah. I mean, I I just don't know how
you could fade the number one exchange
in the world backing what has this
extremely high chance to be the number
one decks in the world now. And if it's
not number one decks in the world, what
it's going to end up number two decks in
the world. Okay, now go back and look
and you know in so many examples the
number two thing is almost always half
of the value of the number one thing.
Okay, so take half of hype and that's
still 8 to 9x and pretty much the worst
case being number two decks in the
world. your base or best case is it's
going to be bigger than hype. And so
that's a 20x plus programmed. It just
depends on which one do you get. Do you
get hey this Binance Back Dex ends up
being bigger than hype or it ends up
being half of hype? Possibly it goes on
to be two to three to four to five times
bigger than hype. It just depends how
successful does the platform get. Is
that something that you can control? No.
Is it something I can control? Not
really. I can kind of complement it. I
can kind of maybe I've brought a little
awareness to it, but I'm like 1% of the
pie here possibly in Aster, you know?
I'm I'm a [__] CZ would look at me
like a little rat, you know, with how
much money I have compared to him. He
he's like, "Who the [__] are you, man?"
So, it's just like,
>> "Yeah, bro. CZ actually, by the way, he
he paid me $100 to shill it." And I was
like, "Holy crap. $100, man. I'm in."
>> Bro, you haven't been bull posting
anything in 14 months and now you're
you're bull like I thought he must have
paid you $100. Yeah, $100 was enough to
get me to come out, man. That was huge.
>> But it was 100 in Astra and it's 3x
since then, so it's 300 now and we're
we're looking at alltime highs. Um, I
think we can probably wrap it here, man.
I appreciate you coming on. I actually
learned a lot. I was just like I almost
was like in the audience listening. Uh,
I appreciate you as always and thank you
for kind of being that extra conviction.
You know, I saw Aster, I saw and you saw
my tweet about like seeing something
seven times. I saw it once from CZ. I
saw it twice from Money Lord. And then
when I saw you bull posting it the first
time, I was like, I don't need to see it
seven times. Skip that.
>> I'm going in. So
>> yeah, dude. You I said it on a tweet,
man. You have a good instinct. A lot of
people don't give you enough credit cuz
you were early to Pepe, like under 50
million market cap from what I remember,
possibly even lower than that. You were
early to Brett. Uh first off, before we
even talk about Asher, just those two
calls alone, first off, those can pay
for like 50 losses, by the way. Oh, but
people always go in too big on one loss
and then they you know, bro, Pepe when
you got it under 50 million that did
over 200x, right? So like, wait, let's
do the math. Yeah. 20x * 10. Yeah, it's
a 200x. Someone could have literally
just put a,000 bucks, they'd have
$200,000. Then on the next play, if they
didn't put $1,000, but they put $10,000
in, they could have lost like 18 times
and still be in profit. So, I really
don't understand people. I think what
most people do is they hit a win and
then they rotate like all their money
into the next play. And you know if the
next play is ever a loss, oh they just
blow it all and then they want to be
pissed at people. But the truth is like
just these three plays alone like Brett
Pepe and now Aster those three plays
alone that you've spotted early
outperform 99.9% of people because I
know most people didn't get Pepe early
like that. I know most people didn't get
Brett early like that and I know a lot
of people faded after this low. So look
man, I just want to say to people, you
know, like you can't be lose. It's not
it's not about some of the loss losses.
It's about the big wins in the year. Cuz
dude, I in a year I only make like four
to six big wins. It's those big wins
that make me millions and millions and
they make up for all my shitty little
losses of like 50k, 100k, 20k, 10k. Uh
especially you know now I think the more
capital you get the more picky you can
get too but even with less capital you
can still be very picky and you know a
few doubles a year few like I mean bro I
mean you follow Jakey make some 10x 20x
200x bro like that sets you so far but
you just can't take your win and rotate
it all into one big loss you can't do
that so
>> so much alpha I appreciate that I 100%
agree. It's like I've won big and I've
also lost big, you know, and it's like
it sucks, but you just got to keep
pushing. You know, if you gave up, if I
was like, "Oh, I'm never gonna DJ again
because I lost so big on Libra." We
would have missed Aster. So, it's like
every day is a new day, man. And every
every day you have a new opportunity to
change your life in crypto is the
opportunity to do that. I appreciate
you. I'm excited now. I'm even more
excited about the base airdrop. I think
that's going to be massive. Excited
about Brett U and also Aster as well.
So, I appreciate you coming on, my
brother. Thank you for everything you do
in the space and uh we'll be in touch
soon.
>> See you, dude. Bye.
>> Thank you, bro.